[{"instructions":"Let's define a new operation +<sub>6</sub>. This operation will give us a way of combining two of the numbers 0, 1, 2, 3, 4, 5 to get another one of them back. To perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result. (That's why the operation is called +<sub>6</sub>.) <br /><br />For example, 3 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 2, because 3 + 5 = 8, and 8 is bigger than 6, so we subtract 6, and 8 - 6 = 2. So 3 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 2.<br /><br />Similarly, 1 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 5, because 1 + 4 = 5, and 5 is less than 6 so we leave it alone. <br /><br />Click \"Continue\" when you're ready to move on.","rt":71021,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":1,"time_elapsed":106846,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"Now try one on your own! What is 4 +<sub>6</sub> 5? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6< /sub>, y ou start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":"3","response_history":["3"],"rt":16525,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":2,"time_elapsed":123375,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 4 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 3 because 4 + 5 = 9 and 9 - 6 = 3.","rt":2312,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":3,"time_elapsed":125690,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"question":"What is 3 +<sub>6</sub> 2? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"5","response":"5","response_history":["5 "],"rt":5013,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":4,"time_elapsed":130704,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 3 +<sub>6</sub> 2 = 5 because 3 + 2 = 5 and 5 is less than 6.","rt":1562,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":5,"time_elapsed":132268,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"question":"What is 1 +<sub>6</sub> 5? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"0","response_history":["0"],"rt":15435,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":6,"time_elapsed":147705,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 1 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 0 because 1 + 5 = 6 and 6 - 6 = 0.","rt":1371,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":7,"time_elapsed":149078,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"question":"What is 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"2","response":"2","response_history":["2"],"rt":7412,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":8,"time_elapsed":156493,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 = 2 because 1 + 1 = 2 and 2 is less than 6.","rt":1241,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":9,"time_elapsed":157736,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"question":"What is 3 +<sub>6</sub> 0? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum  is 6 or  bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":"3","response_history":["3"],"rt":3744,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":10,"time_elapsed":161482,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 3 +<sub>6</sub> 0 = 3 because 3 + 0 = 3 and 3 is less than 6.","rt":2029,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":11,"time_elapsed":163515,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"question":"What is 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"2","response":"2","response_history":["2"],"rt":4834,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":12,"time_elapsed":168351,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0 "},{"feedback":"Correct! 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 2 because 4 + 4 = 8 and 8 - 6 = 2.","rt":1643,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":13,"time_elapsed":169996,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"question":"What is 1 +<sub>6</sub> 3? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"4","response":"4","response_history":["4"],"rt":3715,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":14,"time_elapsed":173712,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 1 +<sub>6</sub> 3 = 4 because 1 + 3 = 4 and 4 is less than 6.","rt":1304,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":15,"time_elapsed":175019,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"question":"What is 4 +<sub>6</sub> 3? <br /><br /> (Remember , to per form +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"1","response":"1","response_history":["1"],"rt":4602,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":16,"time_elapsed":179623,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 4 +<sub>6</sub> 3 = 1 because 4 + 3 = 7 and 7 - 6 = 1.","rt":1272,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":17,"time_elapsed":180896,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"question":"What is 0 +<sub>6</sub> 5? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"5","response":"5","response_history":["5"],"rt":3551,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":18,"time_elapsed":184449,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 0 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 5 because 0 + 5 = 5 and 5 is less than 6.","rt":1144,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":19,"time_elapsed":185594,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"question":"What is 2 +<sub>6</sub> 5? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"1","response":"1","response_history":["1"],"rt":3661,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":20,"time_elapsed":189256,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 2 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 1 because 2 + 5 = 7 and 7 - 6 = 1.","rt":1243,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":21,"time_elapsed":190500,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"instructions":"Now we're going to discuss a couple special properties of this new operation, +<sub>6</sub> that we've learned. First, notice that the number 0 behaves in a special way under +<sub>6</sub>. Whenever we combine 0 with anything else, we get that same thing back. We'll say that 0 is the <i>identity</i> under +<sub>6</sub>, because when you combine it with something it gives you that identical thing back.","rt":35211,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":22,"time_elapsed":225714,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"instructions":"Now that we know 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>, we're going to make a new definition. We'll say that the <i>inverse</i> of a number is the thing that you combine with it to produce the identity. For example, 5 +<sub>6</sub> 1 = 0, so we say 1 is the inverse of 5 under +<sub>6</sub>, (remember 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>).  Similarl y, 3 is its own inverse under +<sub>6</sub>, because 3 +<sub>6</sub> 3 = 0.","rt":49554,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":23,"time_elapsed":275270,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"Now you try! What is the inverse of 4 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"2","response":"2","response_history":["2"],"rt":9184,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":24,"time_elapsed":284459,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.6-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! The inverse of 4 under +<sub>6</sub> is 2 because 4 +<sub>6</sub> 2 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":1754,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":25,"time_elapsed":286214,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.6-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 1 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse  of an el ement is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"5","response":"5","response_history":["5"],"rt":4432,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":26,"time_elapsed":290647,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.6-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! The inverse of 1 under +<sub>6</sub> is 5 because 1 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":1190,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":27,"time_elapsed":291840,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.6-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 3 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":"3","response_history":["3"],"rt":3156,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":28,"time_elapsed":294998,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.6-0"},{"feedback":"C orrect! The inverse of 3 under +<sub>6</sub> is 3 because 3 +<sub>6</sub> 3 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":1018,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":29,"time_elapsed":296018,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.6-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 2 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"4","response":"4","response_history":["4"],"rt":6545,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":30,"time_elapsed":302565,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.6-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! The inverse of 2 under +<sub>6</sub> is 4 because 2 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":1028,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":31,"time_elapsed":303596,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.6-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 0 under +<sub>6</sub>? <b r /><br  /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"6","response_history":["6"],"rt":5685,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":32,"time_elapsed":309282,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.6-0"},{"feedback":"Sorry, that was incorrect. The inverse of 0 under +<sub>6</sub> is 0 because 0 +<sub>6</sub> 0 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":37714,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":33,"time_elapsed":346999,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.6-0"},{"instructions":"It is also possible to successively apply +<sub>6</sub>, and the operation can simply be performed starting with the left-most pair. For example, 2 +<sub>6</sub> 3 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 3.","rt":43261,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":34,"time_elapsed":390262,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"instructions":"We  have one last definition to learn today, using the successive operations we just learned. Let's start with an example. Under our operation +<sub>6</sub> we can make every other number using just 1: 2 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1, 3 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1, 4 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1, 5 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1, and 0 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1. Because of this, we say that 1 is a <i>generator</i> under +<sub>6</sub>. <br /><br /> However, 2 is not a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 4 = 2 +<sub>6</sub> 2, and 0 = 2 +<sub>6</sub> 2 +<sub>6</sub> 2, but there is no way to make 1, 3, or 5 using just 2.","rt":49184,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":35,"time_elapsed":439450,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"Now you try! Is 3 a generator under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, a generator is an element whic h can ma ke every other element.)","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"No","response":"No","response_history":["No"],"rt":13250,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":36,"time_elapsed":452704,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.9-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 3 is not a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 3 = 3, 0 = 3 +<sub>6</sub> 3, but there is no way to make 1, 2, 4, or 5 using just 3.","rt":19371,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":37,"time_elapsed":472079,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.9-0"},{"question":"Is 5 a generator under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, a generator is an element which can make every other element.)","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"Yes","response":"No","response_history":["No"],"rt":5092,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":38,"time_elapsed":477173,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.9-0"},{"feedback":"Sorry, that's incorrect.  5 is a  generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 5 = 5, 4 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, 3 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, 2 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, 1 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, and 0 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, so you can make all of the numbers under +<sub>6</sub> using 5","rt":20306,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":39,"time_elapsed":497482,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.9-0"},{"question":"Is 4 a generator under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, a generator is an element which can make every other element.)","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"No","response":"Yes","response_history":["Yes"],"rt":28695,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":40,"time_elapsed":526180,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.9-0"},{"feedback":"Sorry, that's incorrect. 4 is not a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, b ecause 4  = 4, 2 = 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4, and 0 = 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4, but there is no way to make 1, 3, or 5 using just 4.","rt":16211,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":41,"time_elapsed":542394,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.9-0"},{"question":"Is 0 a generator under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, a generator is an element which can make every other element.)","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"No","response":"No","response_history":["No"],"rt":7040,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":42,"time_elapsed":549438,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.9-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 0 is not a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 0 = 0, but there is no way to make 1, 2, 3, 4, or 5 using just 0.","rt":9381,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":43,"time_elapsed":558821,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.9-0"},{"instructions":"Now we are going to ask you some questions about a new operation , +<sub> 9</sub>, on the numbers 0, 1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8. It works exactly like +<sub>6</sub>, except now after adding the two numbers you subtract 9 if your result is 9 or greater. <br /><br />We'll give you one practice question with feedback to make sure you understand the new operation. After that, try to complete the remaining questions as accurately as possible.","rt":25746,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":44,"time_elapsed":584570,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"Practice: What is 5 +<sub>9</sub> 5?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"1","response":"1","response_history":["1"],"rt":4976,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":45,"time_elapsed":589549,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.11-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 5 +<sub>9</sub> 5 = 1 because 5 + 5 = 10 and 10 - 9 = 1.","rt":1523,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":46,"time_elapsed":591075,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.11-0"},{"question":"What is 3 +<sub>9</sub> 3?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"6","response":"6","response_history":["6"],"rt":3548,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":47,"time_elapsed":594625,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.11-0"},{"question":"What is 7 +<sub>9</sub> 4?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"2","response":"2","response_history":["2"],"rt":6693,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":48,"time_elapsed":601320,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.11-0"},{"question":"What is 1 +<sub>9</sub> 8?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"0","response_history":["0"],"rt":4609,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":49,"time_elapsed":605932,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.11-0"},{"question":"What is 5 +<sub>9</sub> 4?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"0","response_history":["0"],"rt":4164,"trial_type":"qu estion","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":50,"time_elapsed":610099,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.11-0"},{"question":"What is 6 +<sub>9</sub> 6?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":"3","response_history":["3"],"rt":6007,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":51,"time_elapsed":616109,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.11-0"},{"question":"What is 4 +<sub>9</sub> 1? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"5 because it is less than 9 it stays the same","response_history":["5 because it is less than 9 it stays thes","5 because it is less than 9 it stays the same"],"rt":29133,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":52,"time_elapsed":645245,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.11-0"},{"question":"What is 8 +<sub>9</sub> 4? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"3 because 8 plus 4 is 12 and then you subtract 9 which leaves 3","response_history":["12","1","3 because 8 plus 4 is 12 and then u","3 because 8 plus 4 is 12 and then you subtrat","3 because 8 plus 4 is 12 and then you subtract 9 which leaves 3"],"rt":39384,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":53,"time_elapsed":684632,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.11-0"},{"question":"What is the identity under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"0 is the identity under +9 because if you add any two numbers that add up to nine the answer you get is 0","response_history":["0 is the in","0 is the identity under =","0 is the identity under +9 because if o","0 is the identity under +9 because if you add any two numbers tht ","0 is the identity under +9 because if you add any two numbers tht","0 is the identity under +9 because if you add any two numbers that add  up to k ","0 is the identity under +9 because if you add any two numbers that add up to nine the answer you get is 0"],"rt":201305,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":54,"time_elapsed":885939,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.11-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 5 under +<sub>9</sub>?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"4","response":"4","response_history":["4"],"rt":15551,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":55,"time_elapsed":901495,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.11-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 2 under +<sub>9</sub>?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"7","response":"7","response_history":["7"],"rt":7971,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":56,"time_elapsed":909470,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.11-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 3 under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"6 because if you add 3 and 6 you get 9 and then you subtract 9 and get 0","response_history":["6 because if you add 3 and 6 you get 9 and then you subtract 9 and get 0"],"rt":24303,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":57,"time_elapsed":933776,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.11-0"},{"question":"Is 2 a generator under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"no because you can't make all of the odd numbers using only 2","response_history":["no because you can't make 1, 3 and 5 using  ","no because you can't make 1, 3 and 5 using  on","no because you can't make 1, 3 and 5 using  o","no because you can't make 1, 3 and 5 using  ","no because you can't make 1, 3 and 5 using only 2. ","no because you can't make all of the numbers usuing ","no because you can't make all of the numbers usuing","no because you can't make all of the numbers us uin","no  because you can't make all of the numbers usui","no because you can't make all of the numbers usu","no because you can't make all of the numbers using only 2","no because you can't make all of the onumbers using only 2","no because you can't make all of the odnumbers using only 2","no because you can't make all of the oddnumbers using only 2","no because you can't make all of the odd numbers using only 2"],"rt":61087,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":58,"time_elapsed":994867,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.11-0"},{"question":"Is 3 a generator under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"no, you can't make all of the numbers using only 3","response_history":["no, you can't make all of the numbers ui","no, you can't make all of the numbers using lonle","no, you can't make all of the numbers using lonl","no, you can't make all of the numbers using lon"," no, you  can't make all of the numbers using lo","no, you can't make all of the numbers using l","no, you can't make all of the numbers using only 3"],"rt":56926,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":59,"time_elapsed":1051795,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.11-0"},{"question":"Is 5 a generator under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"You can make all of the numbers using only 5 ","response_history":["I bei","I be","I b","I ","I","You can make all of the number ","You can make all of the numbers using only 5 "],"rt":89420,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":60,"time_elapsed":1141218,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.11-0"},{"question":"Is 6 a generator under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"there is no way to make all of the numbers usin g only 6 ","response_history":["there is no way to make all of hte n","there is no way to make all of hte ","there is no way to make all of hte","there is no way to make all of ht","there is no way to make all of h","there is no way to make all of the numbers using i","there is no way to make all of the numbers using only 6"],"rt":26747,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":61,"time_elapsed":1167970,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.11-0"},{"instructions":"Now we'd like to ask you some questions about +<sub>n</sub>, where n could be any postive counting number. For example, n could be 3, or n could be any other counting number you can think of. If you need to write the operation, you can use \"+_n\", and your answers can include n to stand in for the arbitrary value if necessary.","rt":27594,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":62,"time_elapsed":1195568,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"What is the formula for the inverse of 1 under + <sub>n</ sub>?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"n-1","response":"1 +n n-1","response_history":["1 +n n-1"],"rt":165001,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":63,"time_elapsed":1360572,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"question":"What is the formula for the inverse of an element x under +<sub>n</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"n-x","response":"x +n n-x  The inverse is the difference between n and x. ","response_history":["x +n n-x  The inverse is the ","x +n n-x  The inverse is the","x +n n-x  The inverse is th","x +n n-x  The inverse is t","x +n n-x  The inverse is wha","x +n n-x  The inverse is wh","x +n n-x  The inverse is w","x +n n-x  The inverse is the difference between n and x. "],"rt":130022,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":64,"time_elapsed":1490598,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"question":"Is there a pa ttern to  which elements are generators? How can you know if an element x is a generator under +<sub>n</sub> without seeing whether it can make all the elements?.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"there is likely a pattern using different values for n","response_history":["there is likely a pattern using the ","there is likely a pattern using different f","there is likely a pattern using different values for n"],"rt":137121,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":65,"time_elapsed":1627723,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"question":"True or false: If x is an odd number, it must be a generator under +<sub>n</sub>.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["True","False"],"correct_response":"False","response":"True","response_history":["True"],"rt":30892,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":66,"time_elapsed":1658620,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"question":"True or false: If x is an even nu mber, it  must not be a generator under +<sub>n</sub>.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["True","False"],"correct_response":"False","response":"False","response_history":["False"],"rt":5110,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":67,"time_elapsed":1663734,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"question":"True or false: If x is not a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, x must divide n.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["True","False"],"correct_response":"False","response":"True","response_history":["True"],"rt":16377,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":68,"time_elapsed":1680114,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"question":"True or false: If x is not a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, x must be a multiple of a divisor of n. Please explain in words why your answer is corret.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"True","response":"That will mean that it can divide to make all of the other numbers. ","response_history":["That will mean that it can divide to make all of the other numbers. "],"rt":80174,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":69,"time_elapsed":1760291,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"question":"If an element x is a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, is its inverse a generator under +<sub>n</sub> always, sometimes, or never?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Always","Sometimes","Never"],"correct_response":"Always","response":"Always","response_history":["Always"],"rt":35103,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":70,"time_elapsed":1795398,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"question":"if an element x is a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, is x +<sub>n</sub> x a generator under +<sub>n</sub> always, sometimes, or never? Please explain in words why your answer is corret.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"sometimes","response":"sometimes because the second number could be a completely different nu mber for  instance 1 and 2 and they might not both be generators. ","response_history":["Always because ","A","Never because that would ","Never because that would","Never because the second number would be 0 and that can't genear","Never because the second number would be 0 and that can't genea","Never because the second number would be 0 and that can't generate all of the nm","Never because the second number would be 0 and that can't generate all of the numbers. ","Never because the second number could be a couple","Never because the second number could be a coupl","Never because the second number could be a coup","Never because the second number could be a cou","Never because the second number could be a completely df","Never because the second number could be a completely differnt ","Never because the second number could be a completely differnt","Never because the second number could be a completely differn","Never because the second number could be a completely differ","Never b ecause t he second number could be a completely diffee","Never because the second number could be a completely different number for instant ","Never because the second number could be a completely different number for instant","Never because the second number could be a completely different number for instance t","Never because the second number could be a completely different number for instance  1","Never because the second number could be a completely different number for instance  ","Never because the second number could be a completely different number for instance 1 and 2 and they might not both be geneartor","Never because the second number could be a completely different number for instance 1 and 2 and they might not both be genearto","Never because the second number could be a completely different number for instance 1 and 2 and they might not both be geneart","Never because the second number could be a completely different number for instance 1 and 2 and they might not both  be gene ar","Never because the second number could be a completely different number for instance 1 and 2 and they might not both be genea","Never because the second number could be a completely different number for instance 1 and 2 and they might not both be generao","Never because the second number could be a completely different number for instance 1 and 2 and they might not both be generators. ","so because the second number could be a completely different number for instance 1 and 2 and they might not both be generators. ","som because the second number could be a completely different number for instance 1 and 2 and they might not both be generators. ","some because the second number could be a completely different number for instance 1 and 2 and they might not both be generators. ","somet because the second number could be a completely different number for instance 1 and 2 and they might not both be generators. ","sometim because the second number could be a completely differen t number  for instance 1 and 2 and they might not both be generators. ","sometime because the second number could be a completely different number for instance 1 and 2 and they might not both be generators. ","sometimes because the second number could be a completely different number for instance 1 and 2 and they might not both be generators. "],"rt":138434,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":71,"time_elapsed":1933836,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"question":"If an element x is not a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, is x +<sub>n</sub> x a generator under +<sub>n</sub> always, sometimes, or never?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Always","Sometimes","Never"],"correct_response":"Never","response":"Sometimes","response_history":["Sometimes"],"rt":18208,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":72,"time_elapsed":1952048,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"instructions":"We would like to ask you some questions about your background.  Please p ress \"Continue\" to continue.","rt":2273,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":73,"time_elapsed":1954324,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"What is your age?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"38","response_history":["38"],"rt":3496,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":74,"time_elapsed":1957823,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"What is your level of education?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Did not graduate high school","High school diploma","Some college, no degree","Associates Degree","Bachelors Degree","Some graduate school, no degree","Masters Degree","Doctorate, M.D., etc."],"correct_response":"","response":"Bachelors Degree","response_history":["Bachelors Degree"],"rt":2491,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":75,"time_elapsed":1960315,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"What is the most advanced math clas s you've  completed? If you have multiple classes and you're not sure which one is most advanced, please list them.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"Statistics, pre calculus","response_history":["Statistics, pre algeb","Statistics, pre alge","Statistics, pre alg","Statistics, pre al","Statistics, pre a","Statistics, pre calculou","Statistics, pre calculo","Statistics, pre calculus"],"rt":16829,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":76,"time_elapsed":1977147,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"How familiar are you with the concept of modular arithmetic?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - never heard of it","2 - heard of it but didn't know what it was","3 - seen it used or explained","4 - used it but not often or recently","5 - used it, remember and understand it"],"correct_response":"1","response":"1 - never heard of it","response_history":["1 - never heard of it"],"rt":15296,"trial_type":"que stion","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":77,"time_elapsed":1992446,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"How familiar are you with the concept of a mathematical group?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - never heard of it","2 - heard of it but didn't know what it was","3 - seen it used or explained","4 - used it but not often or recently","5 - used it, remember and understand it"],"correct_response":"1","response":"4 - used it but not often or recently","response_history":["4 - used it but not often or recently"],"rt":10205,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":78,"time_elapsed":2002653,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"Do you feel you learned something from this HIT?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - not at all","2 - somewhat","3 - definitely"],"correct_response":"1","response":"2 - somewhat","response_history":["2 - somewhat"],"rt":5017,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":79,"time_elapsed":2007673,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"Do you feel you understood the concepts in this HIT?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - not at all","2 - somewhat","3 - definitely"],"correct_response":"1","response":"2 - somewhat","response_history":["2 - somewhat"],"rt":3583,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":80,"time_elapsed":2011257,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"Did you enjoy this HIT?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - not at all","2 - somewhat","3 - definitely"],"correct_response":"1","response":"2 - somewhat","response_history":["2 - somewhat"],"rt":3344,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":81,"time_elapsed":2014603,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"What is your gender?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Female","Male","Other"],"correct_response":"","response":"Female","response_history":["Female"],"rt":1860,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":82,"time_elapsed":2016464,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"What is/are your native language(s)? (The languages spoken in your household when you were a child.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"English","response_history":["English"],"rt":4814,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":83,"time_elapsed":2021280,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"Did you use pen and paper at any point on this HIT?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"no","response_history":["no"],"rt":3464,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":84,"time_elapsed":2024746,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"Do you have any comments on this HIT?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"none","response_history":["I understood everyth","I unde","I und","I un","I uf","I u","I felt like I n","I felt like I unde rstood e verything exe","I felt like I understood everything except t","I felt like I understood everything except i didnt ","I felt like I understood everything except i didnt","I felt like I understood everything except i didn","I felt like I understood everything except i didn't fully unders","none"],"rt":32970,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":85,"time_elapsed":2057718,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"}]